http://www.monessenhearth.com/about-monessen/privacy-policy

ihy5rb5hfrv3r1skkl040gdy
{"rawurl":"/about-monessen/privacy-policy","sitecode":"MON","site":"MonessenHearth","sitebrandname":"Monessen Hearth","siterootpath":"/sitecore/content/monessenhearth home/","environment":"Production","sessionid":"ihy5rb5hfrv3r1skkl040gdy","viewedcoupon":false,"issyndicatedsession":false,"dealerid":"","lastlocatorsearch":"","debugtracking":false,"ip":"72.182.10.230","brandfilter":"MON","visitedproducts":[],"visitedcategories":[],"ppccampaignid":"","configuratorUserData":""}
Test Json Load |
Test Service Call
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
About MonessenPrivacy Policy
Welcome to vermontcastings.com, monessenhearth.com, majesticproducts.com or ambienttechnologies.com, an online service operated by Monessen Hearth Systems Company and its’ subsidiaries (“MHSC,” “us”, “we”, or “our”). Please read the following
to learn more about our Privacy Policy, which includes compliance with California Privacy Rights (see also
http://www.privacyprotection.ca.gov).
We respect your privacy and are committed to
protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through our Website. We have adopted this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may
disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through our Website and does not apply to
our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of
Use posted on our Website, sets forth the general rules and policies
governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
We generally keep this Privacy Policy posted on our Website and you should review it frequently, as it may change from
time to time without notice. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy. WHEN YOU ACCESS OUR WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE, IMMEDIATELY
STOP ACCESSING OUR WEBSITE. If, at any point, we decide to use your
personally identifiable information in a manner materially different
than what was stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you of
this change by e-mail to the last e-mail address provided to us. You will have a choice (by means of an “opt out” opportunity) as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which your
information was collected if you opt out of the new policy.
INFORMATION WE COLLECTOur Website typically collects two kinds of
information about you: (a) information that you provide that personally
identifies you; and (b) information that does not personally identify
you, that we automatically collect when you visit our Website or that you provide us.
Personally Identifiable Information: Our definition of personally identifiable information includes any
information that may be used to specifically identify or contact you, such as your name, mail address, phone number, etc. As a general
policy, we do not automatically collect your personally identifiable
information when you visit our Website. In certain circumstances, we may request, allow or otherwise provide you an opportunity to submit your personally identifiable information in connection with a feature, program, promotion or some other aspect of our Website. For instance, you may: (a) provide your name, mail address, email address, phone number and other information when registering for a sales promotion on
our Website, when requesting information from us, etc.; (b) provide certain demographic information about you (e.g., age, gender, purchase
preference, usage frequency, etc.) when responding to a survey, poll or
similar request; or (c) post a general comment and/or recommendation on our Website. Certain information may not be personally identifiable
when standing alone (e.g., your age), but may become so when combined with other information (e.g., your age and name). Whether or not you
provide this information is your choice; however, in many instances this
type of information is required to participate in the particular
activity, realize a benefit we may offer, or gain access to certain
content on our Website.
Non-Personal Information:
Our definition
of non-personal information is any information that does not personally
identify you.
Non-personal information can include certain personally
identifiable information that has been de-identified; that is,
information that has been rendered anonymous.
We obtain non-personal
information about you from information that you provide us, either
separately or together with your personally identifiable information.
We also automatically collect certain non-personal information from you
when you access our Website.
This information can include, among other
things, IP addresses, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet
Explorer, Firefox, Safari, etc.), the third party website from which
your visit originated, the operating system you are using (e.g., Vista,
Windows XP, Mac OS, etc.), the domain name of your Internet service
provider (e.g., America Online, NetZero, etc.), the search terms you use
on our Website, the specific web pages you visit, and the duration of
your visits.
HOW WE USE & SHARE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED
Personally Identifiable Information: The
personally identifiable information you submit to us is generally used
to carry out your requests, respond to your inquiries, better serve you,
or in other ways naturally associated with the circumstances in which
you provided the information.
We may share your information with
Majestic™ or Vermont Castings™ dealers or distributors who we feel can
help meet your needs based on your activities on our Website. We may also use this information to later contact you for a variety of reasons, such as customer service, providing you promotional information for our
products, subsidiaries or other affiliated companies, or to communicate
with you about content or other information you have posted or shared
with us via our Website. You may opt-out from receiving future
promotional information from us or those that we share information with, or direct that we not share your information with others, as set forth below.
In certain instances we may also share your
personally identifiable information with our third party vendors performing functions on our behalf – e.g., vendors that administer our
promotions, provide us marketing or promotional assistance, analyze our data, assist us with customer service, etc. Our vendors agree to use
this information, and we share information with them, only to carry out our requests. In addition, we may share your personally identifiable information with participating sponsors to a program or promotion (e.g.,
a sweepstakes or contest) you enter via our Website. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, our Terms of and Conditions, or when you submit the information, your personally identifiable information will not be shared or sold to any third parties without your prior approval.
Non-Personal Information: We use
non-personal information in a variety of ways, including to help analyze
site traffic, understand customer needs and trends, carry out targeted
promotional activities, and to improve our services. We may use your
non-personal information by itself or aggregate it with information we
have obtained from others. We may share your non-personal information with others to achieve these objectives and others, but remember that
aggregate information is anonymous information that does not personally identify you.
OTHER USES & INFORMATION
IP Addresses: An IP address is a number
that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing
the Internet. Web servers (computers that “serve up” web pages)
automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When visitors
request pages from our Website, our servers typically log their IP
addresses. We collect IP addresses for purposes of system
administration, to report non-personal aggregate information to others,
and to track the use of our Website.
IP addresses are considered
non-personal information and may also be shared as provided above.
It
is not our practice to link IP addresses to anything personally
identifiable; that is, the visitor’s session will be logged, but the
visitor remains anonymous to us. However, we reserve the right to use IP
addresses to identify a visitor when we feel it is necessary to enforce
compliance with our Website rules or to: (a) fulfill a government
request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law or legal process;
(c) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Website, or
other users; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of
our Website’s users or the general public.
Cookies, etc.: “Cookies” are small text
files from a website that are stored on your hard drive. These text
files make using our Website more convenient by, among other things,
saving your passwords and preferences for you. Cookies themselves do not
typically contain any personally identifiable information. We may
analyze the information derived from these cookies and other
technological tools we employ (such as clear gifs/web beacons) and match
this information with data provided by you or another party.
For
example, we may use Cookies to determine the effectiveness of our online
advertising.
We may provide our analysis and certain non-personal
information to third parties (who may in turn use this information to
provide advertisements tailored to your interests), but this will not
involve disclosing any of your personally identifiable information.
If you are concerned about the storage and use
of Cookies, you may be able to direct your internet browser to notify
you and seek approval whenever a cookie is being sent to your hard
drive. You may also delete a Cookie manually from your hard drive
through your internet browser or other programs. Please note, however,
that some parts of our Website will not function properly or be
available to you if you refuse to accept a cookie or choose to disable
the acceptance of Cookies.
Email Communications: If you send us an
email with questions or comments, we may use your personally identifiable information to respond to your questions or comments, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference. For
security reasons, we do not recommend that you send non-public personal
information, such as passwords, social security numbers, or bank account
information, to us by email.
However, aside from our reply to such an
email, it is not our standard practice to send you email unless you
request a particular service or sign up for a feature that involves email communications, it relates to purchases you have made with us (e.g., product updates, customer support, etc.), we are sending you information about our other products and services, or you consented to
being contacted by email for a particular purpose. In certain instances, we may provide you with the option to set your preferences for
receiving email communications from us; that is, agree to some communications but not others. You may “opt out” of receiving future
commercial email communications from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link included at the bottom of most emails we send, or as provided
below; provided, however, we reserve the right to send you transactional
emails such as customer service communications.
Transfer of Assets: As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or all (or substantially all) of our assets, the personally identifiable information and non-personal information we have about you
will be transferred to and used by this acquiring entity, though we will
take reasonable steps to ensure that your preferences are followed. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or
against us, all such information may be considered an asset of ours and
as such may be sold or transferred to third parties.
Other: Notwithstanding anything herein to
the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose any personally
identifiable or non-personal information about you if we are required to
do so by law, with respect to copyright and other intellectual property
infringement claims, or if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of
the law or legal process; (c) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Website, or other users; or (d) in an emergency to protect
the health and safety of our Website’s users or the general public.
Your California Privacy Rights:
Residents
of the State of California, under certain provisions of the California
Civil Code, have the right to request from companies conducting business
in California a list of all third parties to which the company has
disclosed certain personally identifiable information as defined under
California law during the preceding year for third party direct
marketing purposes. You are limited to one request per calendar year. In
your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California
resident and provide a current California address for our response. You
may request the information in writing at: info@mhsc.com.
CHILDRENThe features, programs, promotions and other
aspects of our Website requiring the submission of personally
identifiable information are not intended for children.
We do not
knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children
under the age of 13.
If you are a parent or guardian of a child under
the age of 13 and believe he or she has disclosed personally
identifiable information to us please contact us at info@mhsc.com. A
parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 may review and request
deletion of such child’s personally identifiable information as well as
prohibit the use thereof.
KEEPING YOUR INFORMATION SECUREWe have implemented security measures we
consider reasonable and appropriate to protect against the loss, misuse
and alteration of the information under our control.
Please be advised,
however, that while we strive to protect your personally identifiable
information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of
any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not
responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of
your personally identifiable information. In the unfortunate event that
your “personally identifiable information” (as the term or similar terms
are defined by any applicable law requiring notice upon a security
breach) is compromised, we may notify you by e-mail (at our sole and
absolute discretion) to the last e-mail address you have provided us in
the most expedient time reasonable under the circumstances; provided,
however, delays in notification may occur while we take necessary
measures to determine the scope of the breach and restore reasonable
integrity to the system as well as for the legitimate needs of law
enforcement if notification would impede a criminal investigation. From
time to time we evaluate new technology for protecting information, and
when appropriate, we upgrade our information security systems.
OTHER SITES/LINKSOur Website may link to or contain links to
other third party websites that we do not control or maintain, such as
in connection with purchasing products referenced on our Website and
banner advertisements. We are not responsible for the privacy practices
employed by any third party website. We encourage you to note when you
leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of all third party
websites before submitting any personally identifiable information.
CONTACT & OPT-OUT INFORMATIONYou may contact us as at info@mhsc.com if: (a)
you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy; (b) wish to
make corrections to any personally identifiable information you have
provided; (c) want to opt-out from receiving future commercial
correspondence, including emails, from us or our affiliated companies;
or (d) wish to withdraw your consent to sharing your personally
identifiable information with others.
We will respond to your request and, if
applicable and appropriate, make the requested change in our active
databases as soon as reasonably practicable.
Please note that we may
not be able to fulfill certain requests while allowing you access to
certain benefits and features of our Website.
SOLE STATEMENTThis Privacy Policy as posted on this Website
is the sole statement of our Privacy Policy with respect to this
Website, and no summary, modification, restatement or other version
thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, is valid
unless we post a new or revised policy to the Website.
×
Why are you contacting us?
Need a Quote
Need Service
Looking for Help Choosing a Product
Have a Question About My Fireplace
Processing...
Submit
Thank You!
A local dealer will contact you, we look forward to helping you.
Contact a Hearth Expert
Call Me Back
Need help? A dealer in your local area can help you with sales, service and support.Complete the form below and your local dealer will be in touch.
Please fill in your contact information below and a local dealer will contact you directly about your project.
GeoCountry:
